<?xml version="1.0"?>
<products>

<product name="Iphone 16 GB">
	<description>A remarkably slim design that still makes room for a larger display and a faster chip. Ultrafast wireless that does not sacrifice battery life. &#xD;
	fit comfortably. So much went into this iPhone. So you could get even more out of it.</description>
	<price>740.99</price>
	<quantity>10</quantity>
	<image_name>Bubblegum_2012-03-26_03-18-54.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>8</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Samsung Galaxy SIII">
	<description>
	The Samsung Galaxy S III is now easier, faster and even more beautiful than before. Experience the innovative features of Android 4.1, Jelly Bean. 
	With new ways to share stories and discover music; camera enhancements for more creative photos; TecTile technology 
	that adds a new level of functionality; and much more.
	</description>
	<price>584.99</price>
	<quantity>9</quantity>
	<image_name>galaxy3.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Nokia Lumia 920">
	<description>4G LTE Nokia Lumia 920 with Windows Phone 8 was built for amazing clarity, power and speed that lets you capture, share and relive moments as if you were still there. &#xD;
	You will enjoy a rich user-experience in almost any conditions with the stunning 4.5-inch PureMotion HD.</description>
	<price>627.00</price>
	<quantity>10</quantity>
	<image_name>Bubblegum_2012-03-26_03-18-54.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>5</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Windows Phone 8X HTC">
	<description>Honey Boo Bpo</description>
	<price>499.99</price>
	<quantity>3</quantity>
	<image_name>Bubblegum_2012-03-26_03-18-54.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Iphone 5 64GB">
	<description>A remarkably slim design that still makes room for a larger display and a faster chip. Ultrafast wireless that does not &#xD;
comfortably. So much went into this iPhone. So you could get even more out of it.</description>
	<price>1000</price>
	<quantity>10</quantity>
	<image_name>Bubblegum_2012-03-26_03-18-54.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>23</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Droid DNA by HTC">
	<description>
	DROID DNA by HTC impresses with an industry-leading, 5-inch, 1080p full-HD display: one of the first smartphones to feature a 1080p display. 
	The amazing front and rear cameras capture every moment and the Snapdragon quad-core processor offers tremendously fast performance.
	</description>
	<price>500.00</price>
	<quantity>12</quantity>
	<image_name>droid.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Samsung Galaxy Note II">
	<description>
	Looking for the smartphone that can do it all? The Galaxy Note II is a powerhouse of productivity. 
	The S Pen brings the simplicity of pen and paper to innovative mobile technology, 
	plus the ability to perform multiple tasks at once. Quickly create and edit documents, and navigate with the precision of a mouse.
	</description>
	<price>674.99</price>
	<quantity>5</quantity>
	<image_name>note2.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Galaxy Nexus">
	<description>
	The Galaxy Nexus comes with Google Wallet, turning your phone into a virtual wallet to pay for purchases using NFC. 
	Google Wallet works with Citi Mastercard to pay for your purchase at any store with a MasterCard PayPass kiosk.
	</description>
	<price>382.99</price>
	<quantity>3</quantity>
	<image_name>nexus.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>300</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Blackberry Bold 9900">
	<description>
	Create and connect like never before, swiping, pinching and zooming on the Liquid Graphics touch screen. 
	Together with a 1.2 GHz processor, and a 24-bit high-res display, Liquid Graphics gives you fluid animations and instant response times.
	</description>
	<price>399.99</price>
	<quantity>10</quantity>
	<image_name>bold9900.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Blackberry Torch 9850">
	<description>
	Powered by the new BlackBerry 7 OS and Liquid Graphics, 
	your photos, videos, games and apps come to life in incredible detail on the large screen.
	</description>
	<price>241.19</price>
	<quantity>4</quantity>
	<image_name>torch9850.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Blackberry Curve 9310">
	<description>
	Get connected in an instant with the dedicated BBM shortcut key on the BlackBerry Curve 9310 smartphone. 
	One touch launches the BBM app so you can chat in real time or share pictures, videos and files. 
	Plan a night out with a group message, or chat privately one-to-one.
	</description>
	<price>213.19</price>
	<quantity>56</quantity>
	<image_name>curve.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>200</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Porsche Design P9981">
	<description>
	The instantly identifiable Porsche Design ID includes a premium forged stainless steel frame, rich, 
	genuine leather backing, wide iconic BlackBerry QWERTY keyboard and large, luxurious full-touch screen.
	</description>
	<price>2075.00</price>
	<quantity>8</quantity>
	<image_name>porsche.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>1675.00</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Google Nexus 4">
	<description>
	Nexus 4 is the new smartphone from Google. With cutting edge hardware, the latest version of Android, 
	and the best Google apps -- Nexus 4 puts the information at your fingertips.
	</description>
	<price>349.00</price>
	<quantity>3</quantity>
	<image_name>nexus4.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Samsung Galaxy Note">
	<description>
	The Galaxy Note is as convenient to carry as a phone, but comes with all the power of a tablet. Sketch in the park, make annotations on a plane, upload documents, 
	play movies and games with ease using the dual- core processor. The power will always be with you.
	</description>
	<price>499.99</price>
	<quantity>9</quantity>
	<image_name>note1.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="Samsung Galaxy SII">
	<description>
	The Samsung Galaxy S II raises the bar on picture quality with the 4.52" Super AMOLED Plus Display. Colors are deep and vivid. Detail is razor sharp. 
	It's also energy efficient to prolong battery life. 
	Not only is the color hard to believe, but so is the slender 9.59mm thickness and 4.55 ounce weight.
	</description>
	<price>439.00</price>
	<quantity>1</quantity>
	<image_name>galaxy2.jpg</image_name>
	<sale_price>0</sale_price>
</product>

<product name="dsds"><description>dsdsds</description><price>444</price><quantity>5</quantity><image_name>13112010632.jpg</image_name><sale_price>6</sale_price></product><product name="ererrere"><description>dsds</description><price>45</price><quantity>23</quantity><image_name>07112010629.jpg</image_name><sale_price>5</sale_price></product><product name="Robb"><description>Krasnow</description><price>55</price><quantity>4</quantity><image_name>bold9900.jpg</image_name><sale_price>45</sale_price></product></products>
